invitationsbydawn.com 2008-06-23

# Invitations by Dawn - Unique Theme Wedding Invitations and Accessories

This policy last was updated on July 31, 2002.  
At InvitationsbyDawn.com, we respect our customers and understand that you are concerned about privacy, so we've instituted policies intended to ensure that your personal information is handled safely and responsibly. We also have posted this privacy policy to let you know what kind of information we collect, how it is handled, with whom it may be shared, what choices you have regarding our use of your information, and how you may access some of the data you provide to us.

As we continue to develop our website and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we offer, this policy likely will change. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. You can always find our most current version of our privacy policy on this page.

If you have any questions about this policy, please contact us via e-mail at [contact@invitationsbydawn.com](mailto:contact@invitationsbydawn.com) or write us at the following address:

Invitations by Dawn  
681 Main Street P.O. Box 100  
Lumberton NJ 08048-0100

What Information Do We Collect?  
We collect various types of information depending upon how you use our site.

* When you order from us, we collect your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number, and credit card number (with expiration date) and we will retain a record of your purchases.

When you register with us we also may ask for additional information, but you have the option not to provide it. We gather this information in order to offer services and promotions that may be of interest to you.

* When you enter a sweepstakes or contest online, we usually collect your name, address, email address, and phone number. We also may ask you for additional information, such as your age, interests, product preferences, or zip code.

* When you submit a question to customer service, we need your email address to respond, and you also may provide us with various additional information to help us answer your question.

* We also may receive some information about you from other sources and may add it to your account information. For example, we might get your updated address from a shipper or information on your preferences from another website conducting a promotion or event with us.

* We may acquire customer lists from other parties so that we may invite new people to visit our site. Our policy is to acquire only lists of people who have indicated that they are willing to receive email offers. Also, each time we send an email offer, we provide people with the opportunity to opt out of receiving future email offers.

What Are Cookies and Do We Use Them?  
A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a website that is saved on your hard disk by your computer's browser. It holds information a site may need to interact with you and personalize your experience. We use two kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies.

Session cookies exist only for as long as your browser remains open. Once you exit your browser, they go away. We use session cookies to maintain information we need to have in order for you to shop. For example, the Session ID cookie that we ask your browser to hold retains the ID for your shopping cart. Without the Session ID cookie, you can't add merchandise to your shopping cart and carry it to checkout.

Persistent cookies, in contrast, last from visit to visit; they do not go away when you exit your browser. We use persistent cookies to give you a more personalized shopping experience and to help you navigate our store more efficiently. We will use your information to enhance your site experience. However, you can use our site without accepting a persistent cookie. To do so, you should set your browser options to reject persistent cookies. Alternatively, you can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, which gives you the opportunity to decide whether you want to accept it or not. In many instances, the Help button on your browser toolbar will tell you how you can take these steps.

Cookies can be used by a website to recognize you. But that does not necessarily mean any personal information is stored in the cookies. We store no personal information about you in the cookies. Anything you choose to tell us about yourself (such as your address and email address) is stored safely and separately on our secured servers.  
We also use cookies to look at how groups, rather than individuals, use our website. On the web, cookies help us develop an understanding of what areas of our website are of greatest use or interest to our visitors so that we can continue to improve the arrangement, product offerings, and merchandise placement.

How Do We Use Your Information?  
We may use your information in a number of ways, including the following: 

* To improve the content on our website. For example, we may use cookies to find out which parts of our site or our products are visited most often.

* To enhance your online shopping experience. For example, we may use it to recognize you and welcome you to the site.

* For marketing and promotional purposes. For example, we send out emails to our customers about products or events that we think may be of interest to them. We also may send you offers for discounts or free services (e.g., free gift wrap or shipping) on our site.

Do We Share Your Information?  
The information gathered may be shared with corporate affiliates of ours. We also share the information with third parties, including responsible companies with which we have a relationship. For example: 

* Some of our vendors may work closely with us to create a vendor shop within our site or to ship your order directly to you. In certain instances, we may share certain information about you with that vendor (e.g., if you decide to buy their products).

* You also may make a purchase from us through a link from another website or search engine and may use their express checkout tool to do so. When you do, please be aware that both our site and that website or search engine will receive your information.

* In some cases, we may enter into a co-branding relationship with another website that offers you products or services that supplement our assortment (e.g., flowers). In those cases, you may link from our site to another site to purchase the item. In that case, both our site and the other website may receive your information.

* We may team with another website to conduct a sweepstakes or other event (e.g., a live web chat). In those cases, each of the participating websites may collect or receive personal information from you.

* For some of our products, we may provide you with a link to the supplier of that product so that you may get further information. If you link to the supplier's site, the supplier may collect or receive information about you.

* Like other companies, we may use an outside company to place advertising banners or links on other sites or to permit other companies to place advertising on our site. In certain cases, the advertiser may collect information on people who click on the banner or link.

In most of the above situations, these third parties will receive your information because you will be visiting their websites or using their links and, in doing so, you may provide information directly to them. You therefore should refer to their privacy policies to understand how they handle your information and what kinds of choices you have.  
We also may share your personal information with outside companies that perform services for us. For example, we may retain an outside company to manage a database containing certain customer information or to create and distribute an e-mail offering. In those situations, the outside party is performing work for us, and we will take appropriate steps designed to ensure your information is used only to provide the services requested by us, and not for other purposes.

Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law or to protect our interests or property. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, credit bureaus, agents or government agencies in connection with issues related to fraud, credit or debt collection.

And in the event that some or all of our business assets are sold or transferred, we generally would transfer the corresponding information about our customers. Finally, we may share your personal information with unrelated outside companies so that they can directly market their products or services to you if we feel that a company offers products or services that we believe may be of interest. We also may provide you with the opportunity to signup on our website to receive such e-mail offers.

What Choices Do You Have Regarding the Use of Your Information?  
We provide you with a number of choices regarding our handling of your personal information. 

* If you do not want to receive email from us or do not want us to share your information with unrelated third parties for marketing purposes, please follow the steps outlined below to submit a request electronically:

* If you do not want to receive email, please e-mail us at [contact@invitationsbydawn.com](mailto:contact@invitationsbydawn.com) with the subject line "NO EMAIL". (Please note that every time we send you an email, we will give you the option to unsubscribe from our e-mail list, so you'll be able to stop our e-mails at any time).

* If you do not wish your information to be shared with unrelated third parties for marketing purposes, please e-mail us at [contact@invitationsbydawn.com](mailto:contact@invitationsbydawn.com) with the subject line "KEEP PRIVATE".

* If you wish both steps to be taken, please e-mail us at [contact@invitationsbydawn.com](mailto:contact@invitationsbydawn.com) with the subject line "NO E-MAIL/KEEP PRIVATE" as the subject line of your message.

Note: Once you have submitted your request you should assume that it has been successfully received and your request is being processed. Please allow us 14 days from when the request was received to complete the removal, as some of our promotions may already have been in process before you submitted your request. 

* If you prefer to, you can contact us by writing to the following address: 

Invitations by Dawn  
681 Main Street P.O. Box 100  
Lumberton NJ 08048-0100

If you choose to write to us, please include your name, address and account number (if you have one), and state one of the following: 

a. "NO MAIL OFFERS" (if you don't want to receive offers by mail);  
b. "NO PHONE OFFERS" (if you don't want to receive offers by phone); or  
c. "NO PHONE OR MAIL OFFERS" (if you don't want to receive either).

Because customer lists often are prepared well in advance of an offering (sometimes 3-4 months before the offer is made), you may continue to receive some offers after you send us a request not to use your information for specified marketing purposes. We appreciate your patience and understanding in giving us time to carry out your request.

Can I Access My Information?  
If you have questions about your order you may check your order status online by clicking here.

Questions regarding your charge account can be forwarded to our Customer Service Department. If you would like to email our Customer Service Department please [click here](mailto:contact@invitationsbydawn.com).

Is My Information Secure?  
We are committed to doing our best to maintain the security of information collected on our site. To try to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place the appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
Private account and customer information is located on a secured server behind a firewall; it is not directly connected to the Internet.

Encryption is a process by which a message or information is scrambled while it is in transit to us. It is based on a key that has two different parts, public and private. The public part of the key is distributed to those with whom you want to communicate. The private part is for the recipient's use only. So long as you use a browser that allows for encryption, when you send personal information to us, you use a public key to encrypt your personal information. If your information is intercepted during the transmission, it is scrambled and very difficult to decrypt. Once we receive your encrypted personal information, we use the private part of our key to decode it.

What About Information About Children?  
The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act took effect on April 21, 2000 and imposes certain requirements on websites directed toward children under 13 that collect information on those children, or on websites that know they are collecting information on children under the age of 13. We want to let you know that it currently is our policy not to collect personal information on any person under 13. For this reason, our online sweepstakes are restricted to entrants who, at a minimum, are at least 13.

If this policy changes, we will revise this portion of its privacy policy and will comply with the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, which include providing notice and choice to each child's parent or guardian before collecting personal information.

Thank you for shopping with InvitationsbyDawn.com. If you have any questions about this policy, please contact us via e-mail at [contact@invitationsbydawn.com](mailto:contact@invitationsbydawn.com)  
Legal Information  
©2000 InvitationsbyDawn.com, Inc. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. Please refer to the legal notice below for terms of use.  
This website is operated by InvitationsbyDawn.com. The website address for InvitationsbyDawn.com is http://www.InvitationsbyDawn.com. The mailing address for InvitationsbyDawn.com is InvitationsbyDawn.com, 681 Main Street, P.O. Box 100, Lumberton NJ, 08048-0100.

All users of this website agree that their access to and use of this website are subject to the terms and conditions set forth in this legal notice and all applicable laws, and that any such access or use is undertaken at the user's own risk. These terms and conditions further are subject to change at any time without prior notice. Any such changes will be reflected on the Legal Notice page of the InvitationsbyDawn.com website.   
All content, graphics, code and software used on or incorporated into this website, and the arrangement or integration of all such content, graphics, code and software, are subject to copyrights held by or licensed to InvitationsbyDawn.com, Inc., and all rights thereto are specifically reserved. Permission is granted to electronically copy and print hard copies of pages from this website solely for personal, non-commercial purposes related to the placement of an order or shopping with InvitationsbyDawn.com. Any other use of this website or content or information contained in this website is strictly prohibited, unless the written permission of InvitationsbyDawn.com first is obtained. 

This website may contain typographical errors or inaccuracies and may not be complete or current. InvitationsbyDawn.com therefore reserves the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions (including after an order has been submitted) and to change or update information at any time without prior notice. Please note that such errors, inaccuracies or omissions may relate to pricing and availability. We apologize for any inconvenience. 

This website, and any information or content on this website, are provided "as is," with all faults. InvitationsbyDawn.com makes no representations or warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, with respect to this website or content or information available on or through this website. Except as otherwise provided under applicable laws, neither InvitationsbyDawn.com nor its corporate affiliates, nor the directors, officers, employees, agents, contractors, successors or assigns of each, shall be liable for any damages whatsoever arising out of or related to the use of this website or any other website linked to this website. This limitation of liability applies to direct, indirect, consequential, special, punitive or other damages you or others may suffer, as well as damages for lost profits, business interruption or the loss of data or information, even if InvitationsbyDawn.com is notified in advance of the potential for any such damages. 

InvitationsbyDawn.com and InvitationsbyDawn.com's, as well as page headers, custom graphics, buttons, images and other content on this website, are subject to trademark, service mark, trade dress, copyright and or other proprietary or intellectual property rights or licenses. Other trademarks, product names and company names or logos used on this website are the property of their respective owners. Except as expressly authorized, the use or misuse of any trademarks, trade names, logos, images, graphics or content from this website is strictly prohibited. 

InvitationsbyDawn.com does not make any representations or warranties about any website you may access through this website. Any such website is independent from InvitationsbyDawn.com, and InvitationsbyDawn.com has no control over, or responsibility with respect to, the information provided or activities undertaken by any such website. A link between InvitationsbyDawn.com and another website further does not mean that InvitationsbyDawn.com endorses that website. You need to make your own independent decisions regarding your interactions or communications with any other website. 

InvitationsbyDawn.com does not want to receive confidential, proprietary or trade secret information through this website (excluding information related to any order you submit). Please note that any information, materials, suggestions, ideas or comments sent to InvitationsbyDawn.com will be deemed non-confidential. And, by submitting any such information, you are granting InvitationsbyDawn.com an irrevocable and unrestricted license to use, modify, reproduce, transmit, display and distribute such materials, information, suggestions, ideas or comments for any purpose whatsoever. However, we will not use your name in connection with any such materials, information, suggestions, ideas or comments unless we first obtain your permission or otherwise are required by law to do so.

For more information on Invitations by Dawn.com Customer Service Policies call 1-800-257-9567 .
